

# MAHENDRA NAIDU.P

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER** 

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

ADOBE INDESIGN

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

ADOBE PREMIERE PRO

#### CONTACT



Phone: 8885686434



Email: naidumahi827@gmail.com



Behance: https://behance.net/mahendranaidu

#### **SKILLS**

COMMUNICATION
TYPOGRAPHY
ADOBE'S CREATIVE APPS
LOGO CREATION
SOCIAL MEDIA POSTS

#### **ABOUT ME**

Experienced graphic designer with a keen eye for detail and an enthusiasm for completing assignments on time. Expert in Adobe Creative Suite, especially illustrator and Photoshop. Skills in time management and problem solving that allow for minimal supervision and maximal teamwork.

#### **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2019

Intern Trainee

For the Intership as a graphic designe

2014 - 2017

DIPLOMA (Mechanical) Golden Valley Integrated campus (Madanapalli, chittor dist)

2013 - 2014

Board of Secondary Education BVM High School ( Rayachoty Kadapa dist)

### JOB EXPERIENCES

2022-Still Now

Graphic Designer At Newmark Hyderabad

2021 - 2022

Graphic Designer At Indwell Group Hyderabad

2019 - 2021

Graphic Designer At Macronel India Pvt.Ltd Hyderabad

2018 - 2019

Intern Trainee

At Macronel India Pvt.Lt Hyderabad

#### PERSONAL ACHIEVEMENT

2022

HANDBALL FEDARATION OF INDIA WEBSITE

Designed whole layout for handballindia.com in the span of 1 month and we built the whole structure of the website.

2022

#### HANDBALL FEDERATION OF INDIA PLAYER REGISTRATION

Recently we built the admin interference for HFI form login form to player registration form with admin panel and official ID cards for players.